{
    "id": "13459c80063f48e4a26cc1fef2ff0d0e",
    "title": "Past Simple Or Present Perfect Tense",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "When ………………… from work?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did she return",
                "did she returned",
                "has she returned"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6c3f426a84c241a49c08b84ece15ab95"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… to the US?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Did you ever go",
                "Have you ever been",
                "Did you ever been"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9144f7f9ddef44c5af434dbe33b0f281"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is the most beautiful woman ………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I had ever seen",
                "I have ever seen",
                "I have ever saw"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "932c6422dd2f4d8c8113f8eb75ef2431"
        },
        {
            "question": "That is the best movie …………………… ..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I ever watched",
                "I have ever watched",
                "I did ever watch"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "81836e76a06b40a88d3ecd4bf3be1fc6"
        },
        {
            "question": "That is the most difficult problem …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "I ever had to deal with",
                "I have ever had to deal with",
                "I had to deal with",
                "I ever dealt with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c4df45e868354a03b51024f64e1bbd12"
        },
        {
            "question": "When …………………. I was working in the garden.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "you phoned",
                "have phoned",
                "had phoned"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7a9fdca2bf4349cebe08e8af9426cff2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………… with children before, so I know what to expect in my new job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have worked",
                "worked",
                "had worked"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a830fb94c5794d4784b0b3b629810fda"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. all my childhood in France.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "spent",
                "have spent",
                "had spent"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3f783415df54481ca9425a9433eaa4d5"
        },
        {
            "question": "Who …………………… that necklace?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "gave you",
                "has given you",
                "had given you"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "af199dd5c90448c480d0f46c1fd3b337"
        },
        {
            "question": "There …………………. a plane crash near Bristol last night.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was",
                "has been",
                "had been"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9b525c792aed4801a4b71050e534e6c3"
        }
    ]
}